kdanmobile.com 2016-06-04

# Privacy Policy | Kdan Mobile

This Privacy Policy governs how Kdan Mobile Software Ltd. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users ("Users") of this website ( <http://www.kdanmobile.com/> , "Site"). This Privacy Policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Kdan Mobile Software Ltd (“Kdan”). By visiting the Site and/or purchasing and/or using Kdan’s services, Users accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

* * *

### Personal Information

Personal Information is information about you that is personally identifiable, such as your name, username, password, address, email address, phone number, which is not otherwise publicly available. (“Personal Information”)  
We collect Personal Information to provide better services to Users. Users may be asked for Personal Information, including without limitation, when Users visit our Site, register on the Site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources made available on our Site. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect Personal Information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. In the event that Users refuse to provide Personal Information, please note that it may prevent Users from engaging in certain Site-related activities.

We collect various types of Personal Information for the following services: 
  1. Member registration: name and email address.
  2. Newsletter and/or Blog subscription: name and email address.
  3. Purchasing or trial use of Kdan’s products or services: name, email and credit card details.
  4. Other services or activities such as special marketing or competition events: name, email, country origin and other information related to Kdan’s marketing purposes. 

* * *

### Non-Personal Information

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about Users in the course of the interaction with our Site. Non-personally identifiable information is information that is not personally identifiable about the Users, including without limitation User’s browser name, the type of computer and technical information about User’s means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

* * *

### Web Browser Cookies

Certain information may also be collected, such as your Internet protocol address, device event information including but not limited to browser type, crashes, system activity and other server log information. Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may disable cookies on their web browser, or set the browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. In the event that the web browser is set to refuse cookies, please note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

* * *

### How We Process and Use Collected Information

Kdan Mobile Software Ltd. may process and use User’s Personal Information by mail, phone call and other reasonable legal means for the following purposes (“Purposes”) within the territories and during the period necessary to carry out the Purposes: 
  * #### To Communicate with Users

In the event that Users send to us any comments or inquires on the Site, we will reply to such Users via the contact information provided by Users. 
  * #### To personalize user experience

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. 
  * #### To send newsletters and marketing materials upon subscription

If User subscribes our newsletter on the Site, we will send emails to the subscribers for information related to our Company, such as occasional company news, upcoming events, updates, related product or service information. Detailed instructions to unsubscribe the newsletter are provided at the bottom of such email. User may unsubscribe such newsletter at any time. Upon receiving User’s request to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we will immediately remove User’s email address from our mailing list and stop sending future emails to such User. 
  * #### To administer any features on the Site

If Users enter into a sweepstake, contest, survey, promotion or activities on the Site, we may use the information provided by Users to administer such features. 

* * *

### How We Protect Your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and information security measures to guard against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your Personal Information, transaction information and data processed and stored on our Site.

Our Site is in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

* * *

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or rent User’s personal information to any third party. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the foregoing purposes. We may use third-party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes. If you do not wish to share your information in such manner, please contact us at <http://www.kdanmobile.com/en/contact.html>.

* * *

### Advertising

Advertisements may appear on our Site that are delivered to Users by third-party advertisers, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the advertiser’s server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement and to compile non-personal information about you or whoever use your computer. This information allows advertisers to, among other purposes, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies or any practices by such advertisers.

* * *

### Third-Party Sites

The Site may contain links to third-party websites, products, and services. Our products and services may also use or offer products or services from third parties. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of those third parties. Users are encouraged to review the privacy policies of those third parties.

* * *

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We regularly review our Privacy Policy and our compliance therewith. Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will update our Privacy Policy on this page of our Site if there may be any changes and a notice will be posted along with the update in case of any material change. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically.

* * *

### Your Consent to the Privacy Policy

By using this Site, you consent to our Privacy Policy last updated. If you do not agree with the terms of the Privacy Policy or refuse to provide your Personal Information, you may stop using the services provided through the Site or otherwise Kdan may not be able to provide you with full function of the services. In addition, Kdan reserves the right to terminate or suspend the provision of our services to you if we determine that our Privacy Policy is not observed or incomplete Personal Information has been provided.

* * *

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through the Site and not to information collected offline.

* * *

### Commitment to Your Privacy

To ensure the security of your information and the enforcement of the Privacy Policy, we communicate our policies and regulations and administer supervision to our employees.

* * *

### Your Rights

With respect to your Personal Information provided to us, you may make the following request through contacting Kdan’s Customer Service at <http://www.kdanmobile.com/en/contact.html>: 

  1. make inquiry or request to review your Personal Information ;
  2. request to make duplications of your Personal Information;
  3. request to make supplement or correction of your Personal Information;
  4. request to suspend the collection, processing or using of your Personal Information; or,
  5. request to delete your Personal Information.

* * *

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the data processing, or the operation of this Site, please contact us at: 

  * Kdan Mobile Software Ltd.
  * http://kdanmobile.com/en/contact.html

This Privacy Policy was last updated on December 11, 2015.
